arredatutto.com 2019-05-30

# Privacy Policy

Last updated 11.05.2018. To view the previous terms, click here. 

This privacy statement (hereinafter "  **Privacy Notice**  ") enters into force once accepted by all users who have accepted it during registration on the website www.Arredatutto.com (hereafter the " **Site** ") and from 14/05 / 2018 for all other users. To view the previous terms, click here. 

By visiting the Website, you acknowledge and accept the provisions in this Privacy Notice. 

  1. _Purpose and consent_
  2. _Changes to the Privacy Notice for users;_
  3. _Personal data collected on Arredatutto_  ;
  4. _How we use your personal data;_
  5. _How Arredatutto uses user data according to the choices made;_
  6. _Are Personal Data collected by Arredatutto transferred to third parties?_  ;
  7. _What are the rights of users_  ;
  8. _For how long Arredatutto can store Personal data_  ;
  9. _Children's privacy;_
  10. _Data controllers of personal data_
  11. _How we protect your personal data_  ;
  12. _How to exercise your rights_  ;
  13. _Illicit Uses_  ;
  14. _Usurpation / Phishing (Telematic Collection Finalized for the acquisition of personal data);_
  15. _Security of online payments;_
  16. _Social Network;_
  17. _Cookies and similar technologies._

**_1\. Purpose and consent_**    
This Privacy Notice for users describes the methods of acquisition, use, transmission, storage and protection of personal information (hereinafter "  **Personal Information**  ").   
**Personal Information**  means information and / or data that identifies or identifies a natural person and that could be used to identify it and provide details on its characteristics, habits, and lifestyle.   
The information made anonymous or aggregated is not considered personal so as to no longer allow the identification of a specific physical person, not even in combination with other information or in other ways.   
By using our services and / or registering an account on the Site you accept the provisions of this Privacy Policy for users and you are also consenting to the acquisition, use, transmission, storage and protection of Personal Information as described in the Privacy Notice for users and in accordance with the legislation on personal data ("  **Personal Data**  ").   
If you do not provide the requested information, you may not be able to use all our services.

**_2\. Changes to the Privacy Notice for users_**    
Arredatutto Srl reserves the right to modify this Privacy Notice for users at any time by publishing the relevant forecasts on the Site. All modified provisions come into force 30 days after publication. Any substantial changes to this Privacy Notice for users will be announced in the Privacy area.

**_3\. Personal data collected on Arredatutto_**    
Arredatutto collects Personal Information conferred directly by you and / or acquired automatically through devices (including mobile devices) when: use our services, register a Furnishing account, provide data to Arredatutto, update or add information to your account, or contact Furnishings in another way.   
The Personal Data that Arredatutto receives from users / customers help us to customize and continuously improve your purchases on the Site. Arredatutto uses this data in particular to manage orders, provide products and services, process payments, communicate with you regarding orders, products , services and promotional offers, deliveries, update our records and, in general, manage your account, show content, such as wish lists, and user reviews and recommend products and services that may be of your liking. 

Arredatutto also uses this data to improve its  _online_  store and the service offered, and also to prevent or report fraud or abuse to the detriment of its website and to allow third parties to perform technical, logistical and other activities. on our behalf.   
The Personal Information we collect can be included in the following categories:   
**_Personal Data provided directly by users when using our Services or register an account on Arredatutto:_**

  * Identification data such as name, surname, gender, dates of birth, delivery address, profession, telephone numbers, addresses, e-mail addresses, to which Arredatutto associates an order number;
  * During an order, our bank lenders also collect and process Personal Data relating to your means of payment (credit card number, date and end validity of the credit card, visual cryptogram - given that it will not be stored, etc.). ). For our part, we process the partial number of your credit card consisting of the (6) first numbers and the last four (4) numbers and the expiration date of your credit card as transmitted to us by your bank. Therefore, this payment identifier does not permit the carrying out of bank transactions and is held for a period of fifteen (15) months, except in case of cancellation by you.
  * Information relating to the transaction made (transaction number, purchase details, etc.), or relating to the payment of invoices issued from or via the site (payment methods, discounts granted, receipts, balances and non-payments, or relating to credits subscribed, amount and duration, to the name of the lender, etc.). Some data are mandatory and others optional. Other content generated by you or connected to your account (for example, adding products to the shopping cart or products you observe).
  * Arredatutto collects and processes Personal Data relating to the control of the business relationship with customers: product and / or service purchased, service or subscription signed, quantity, amount, periodicity, address (s) of delivery and / or billing, telephone number, security code, and any other relevant information about the delivery (check number, shipment location, etc.) history of purchases and services, product referral, correspondence and / or telephone exchanges between you and our post service sale, person (s) responsible for the customer relationship, etc.
  * Data relating to shipments, invoices and other, used to purchase or ship a product, as well as information required for customs formalities (for example, identification of a fiscal nature or other identification numbers) and shipping information (for example, codes shipments and related updates).
  * The Personal Data necessary are collected and processed:  _i_  ) to carry out the actions of loyalty, research, study, survey, product testing and promotion;  _ii_  ) the organization and development of eventual contest-games, lotteries and any promotional operation.
  * Data is also collected to store your preferences in terms of communication (channel, content, frequency) and sales display.
  * In some cases, when you use our Services, you may indicate age, gender, interests and preferences.
  * You may also provide other Data by updating or adding information in your account, by resolving disputes or by communicating with Arredatutto in any other way regarding our Services.
  * Other Data that Arredatutto is required or authorized to collect and process, in accordance with current legislation, in order to authenticate or identify the user or to verify the information collected.

It should be noted that when accessing the Site and / or an electronic media published by a third party containing promotional campaigns disseminated by Arredatutto, tracers and / or equivalent technologies, and in particular cookies, resulting from the calculation of fingerprints of your electronic devices used said " fingerprinting ", invisible pixels, etc. (hereinafter the "Cookies"), may be used and / or deposited, which record and / or read files on your terminal, including those of our partners and, to collect and process information in relation to your interaction with our services and, in particular with your browsing and your behavior on the Site.   
Arredatutto collects and treats Personal Data related to your browsing and your behavior on the site, data that are very numerous: IP address, pages visited, brands that interest you, purchases made, etc.   
In this context, subject to your agreement and / or settings of your electronic devices, Arredatutto may also collect and process all the following personal data, or parts thereof.   
Information in connection with the devices you use: 

  * The type of device you use (Smartphone, tablet, computer, etc.);
  * The system used by your device (Mac OS, iOS, Android, Windows, BlackBerry, etc.);
  * The categories and versions of plug-ins of your device;
  * Your Internet access provider (Orange, SFR, Bouygues, Free, etc.);
  * The browser used (Safari, Chrome, Internet explorer, etc.);
  * The advertising identifier linked to the operating system of your device;
  * The IP address of your device;
  * Your language preferences.

Information on our browsing and your behavior on the Website: 

  * the statistics on the consultation of the different pages of our site (for example the category of goods or services presented on the pages you visit, the time you spend there, etc.);
  * the complete URL path to, through and from our site;
  * the categories and versions of plug-ins of your device;
  * confirmation of receipt and reading of commercial, prospecting or information e-mails that we may send to you, subject to your consent.

Information about the sales spaces and / or promotional banners to which you access on the Website, as on third-party supports, the promotional announcements provided to you and, if necessary, that have been provided to you: 

  * The URL and / or the subject of the website and / or the mobile application in which you navigate or have browsed and where the promotional advertisement can be delivered to you and, if appropriate, it has been delivered to you;
  * Details of the announcements that come to you and, if applicable, which have been delivered to you (advertiser's identity, type of announcement, etc.);
  * Your attitude towards this or these announcements (time spent on advertising, your possible clicks, etc.);
  * Your behavior after clicking on or on the ads (download an application, reply to a questionnaire, etc.);
  * The number of times you received the ad or the promotional ads delivered.

Information about you (age or age group, gender, declared and / or alleged socio-professional category, presumed centers of interest, etc.) connected to your activity on the Internet and / or on the Website (depending on the pages consulted, of the products displayed, the searches carried out, etc.).

Finally, Arredatutto collects and processes the data from the parameterization of your account on the Site, such as the frequency and / or time of receiving announcements of our sales, our newsletters, our alerts, etc.

**_Personal data acquired automatically when you use our Services or register a Arredatutto account_**

  * Arredatutto acquires Data when you interact with our Services and your communications with Arredatutto. This data is what we receive from electronic devices (including mobile devices) that you use when you access our services. These can include the following: device type, ad ID, and unique device token.
  * Data on your computer and connection, for example, statistics on page views, inbound and outbound site traffic, source URLs, ad data, IP address, and web log data.

**_Personal data that Arredatutto collects through cookies and similar technologies_**    
Arredatutto uses cookies, unique identifiers and other similar technologies to acquire data on the pages and links visited and other actions that occur when you use our services, within the advertising or email content.

**_4\. How we use your personal data_**    
Arredatutto uses Personal Data collected by users for various purposes related to the performance of our Services, in compliance with current regulations, and to fulfill contractual obligations with users. Below, we indicate how, and on what legal basis, Arredatutto uses your personal data:

  * carry out operations relating to our business relationship, that is to say concerning orders, deliveries, invoices, accounting, the follow-up of the "relationship with the customer", and the implementation of satisfaction surveys, the handling of complaints and the post service -sale, etc .;
  * offer commercial offers also according to your choices;
  * select users registered on the Site to carry out studies, surveys and product tests, as well as loyalty, prospecting and promotion actions;
  * customize our services, in particular through the personalization of the Site according to your preferences found and / or declared, and your needs;
  * personalize our communication to you, through electronic information messages, according to your perceived preferences, your needs and your choices;
  * carrying out commercial solicitation operations;
  * the elaboration of commercial statistics, analysis and marketing tools (especially ranking, score, etc.)
  * the organization of contest games, lotteries or any promotional operation excluding games in the online gambling sector;
  * the management of outstanding debts and disputes;
  * the management of your comments on the Website and / or on the internet pages published by us and hosted on the websites of our Social Networks;
  * to prevent, detect, mitigate and detect fraud, security breaches and potentially prohibited or illegal activities;
  * to enforce our terms of sale, this Privacy Policy or other contractual rules, as well as to monitor restrictions on offers to buy or sell and communications between users for violations of our rules or applicable legislation.

Arredatutto uses your Personal Data to pursue its legitimate interests, without however prevailing over the fundamental rights and freedoms of the users. Arredato has implemented controls for a fair balance between its own interests and those of its users. This implies: 

  * improve the Services, for example, by examining the data on blocked or non-functioning pages visited by users, in order to identify and solve problems;
  * customize, measure and improve advertising based on preferences;
  * contact users by email to offer coupons, discounts and special promotions to inform you about the services offered by Arredatutto, as permitted by current legislation;
  * Introduce targeted marketing campaigns, service updates and promotional offers to users based on the preferences shown;
  * Evaluate the efficiency of marketing e-mail campaigns (for example by analyzing the opening and clicking percentages);
  * Monitor and improve the security of information on the Arredatutto website and on mobile applications.

With the consent of users, Arredatutto may use Personal Data to carry out marketing campaigns via email.   
**Users have the right to withdraw their consent at any time.**

**_5\. as furnishing uses user data according to the choices made_**    
The user can choose the newsletters and promotions he wants to receive from Arredatutto.   
**_Marketing_**    
If you do not want to receive marketing communications, or communication that calls for the conclusion of purchases of products placed in the cart, you can unsubscribe via the link in the received email, change the notification preferences, contact Arredatutto as indicated in the Privacy section. Under no circumstances shall Arredatutto sell or otherwise disclose personal data collected to third parties for marketing purposes.   
**_Advertising_**    
If you do not wish to take advantage of advertising customization programs, you can opt out of the link indicated in the ad in question or contact Arredatutto as indicated in the Privacy section. By canceling the participation, the personalized advertising will be interrupted, but the collection of your personal data will continue as described in the Privacy Notice. Arredatutto does not allow third parties to monitor or collect personal data collected on the site for their advertising purposes.   
**_Keep access active_**    
When you log in to your account for our Services, you can choose to keep your access active for a certain period of time. If you use a public or shared computer, we do not recommend that you maintain access. During the period in which access is maintained, anyone using the computer / browser in question will be able to see most of your account information and perform specific actions without the need for further authorization. Specific actions and account activities that can be performed by computer / browser users include the following:

  * Make offers, purchases and proposals for products;
  * Make payments or add products to the cart;
  * See or modify the products that are observed or the order details;
  * See the profile page;
  * Conduct after-sales activities, cancel orders, request returns or make claims.

**_6\. Are personal data collected by Arredatutto sold to third parties?_**    
Your Personal Data is an important component of our work and is strictly confidential and is not among our activities to transfer it to others.Therefore Personal Data will be communicated only in accordance with the methods described below and for the following purposes.   
**__Service providers and financial institutions, indicated below__  :**

  * Third party suppliers of shipping services (eg TNT, UPS, Schenker, and other carriers) and logistics, with whom we share delivery addresses, contact information and shipping codes to facilitate the delivery of the purchased products and other communications related to delivery;
  * Lenders to make credit card payments, execute transactions etc. etc.

These providers have access only to Personal Data that are necessary to perform their duties. We guarantee that they can not use the same data for other purposes and are also required to process the Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Notice, and in accordance with the applicable regulations on the protection of Personal Data.   
**__Application of the law, legal proceedings and procedures authorized by law__**

  * To enforce the current legislation or apply our General Conditions of Use and Sale and other agreements; to protect our assets or rights, as well as the safety of Arredatutto, our users or other subjects. This includes the exchange of information with other companies and organizations that prevent fraud or reduce credit risk.
  * Authorities or law enforcement agencies or authorized third parties in response to a verified request or other procedure provided for by the law related to a criminal investigation or an unlawful or presumed activity or to any other activity that exposes one of our companies, your person or any other Arredatutto user to a legal responsibility. We will provide the information we deem relevant for investigation or inquiries, such as name, city, county, zip code, telephone number, email address, user ID history, IP address, fraud claim, bid history, and listings.
  * Companies or persons responsible for credit verification authorized by applicable national laws (for example, information on delayed or missed payments or other defaults related to your account that could be reported in the documentation on creditworthiness);

Third parties involved in judicial proceedings, if they perform mandates, court orders or similar legal acts or if we believe in good faith that the provision of data is necessary to prevent physical damage or imminent financial loss or to report alleged illegal activities.   
**__With your consent__**    
In cases other than those indicated above, you will be informed each time your Personal Data will be communicated to third parties and you will have the possibility to choose whether or not to communicate your Personal Data to third parties. Whenever Personal Data is transferred to companies, institutions or institutions based in countries outside the European Community, we will ensure that the Data is transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as required by current legislation on the protection of data in the context of the communication of data to third parties as indicated above.   
**__Transfers of property__**    
In the event of a merger or acquisition with another company, we may share data with the company in accordance with our global privacy standards. In such cases, we will request that the new company born from the merger or acquisition comply with this Privacy Notice regarding your personal data. If we wish to process your Personal Data for purposes not indicated in this Privacy Notice, you will first receive a notification regarding the processing of your Personal Data for new purposes.   
In no case your Personal Data collected by Arredatutto, starting from the Site, will be communicated to the advertisers of advertising.

**_7\. what are the rights of users_**    
In accordance with the Personal Data Regulation, you can:

  * Oppose to the processing of your data for legitimate reasons;
  * Access all of your Data at any time, starting from your account on the Website;
  * Correct, update and delete your Statement Data at any time from your account, provided the reasons are legitimate.
  * Ask for a limitation of the treatments we do for your data.

Moreover, you have the opportunity to communicate to us directives for the storage, deletion and communication of your Personal Data after your death.   
In the absence of any directive, your heirs can contact Arredatuto in order to: 

  * access data processing that allows the organization and regulation of the succession of the deceased;
  * to proceed with the closure of your account on the Site and oppose the further processing of your Personal Data.

In any case, you have the opportunity to inform us, at any time, that you do not wish, in case of death, that your Personal Data will be communicated to third parties.   
If you require Arredatutto to interrupt the processing of some or all of your Personal Data or revoke (if applicable) your consent to our use or our sharing of your personal data for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice, Arredatutto may not be able to provide you with all the Services and customer support offered to our users and authorized pursuant to this Privacy Notice and our User Agreement. 

At your request, we will close the account as soon as possible and will remove your Personal Data, depending on the activities of your account and in compliance with current legislation.   
If you do not want to receive e-mails or other mail from us, you can review your newsletter settings and notification preferences. If you do not want us to use the Personal Information we collect to personalize the third party advertisements that we show you, you can review your Newsletter Settings and notification preferences. In order not to receive any communication regarding the finalization of purchases included in the cart, you can click the link at the bottom of the same email or write to Arredatutto. 

You can always choose not to provide Personal Data, provided that the communication of such data may be necessary to place an order or take advantage of some features of Furnishing such as the completion of the order. 

**_8\. How long furniture can store personal data_**    
The retention period of personal data may vary depending on the context of the Services we provide and our legal obligations. Retention periods normally depend on the following factors: 

  * To maintain and improve the efficiency of our services and product quality, maintaining the security of our systems and maintaining commercial and tax records. These are the general rules on which most of the conservation periods are based on Arredatutto.
  * If personal data is sensitive, there will be a shorter retention period.

When it is no longer necessary to keep personal data, these will be removed in a secure manner in accordance with our rules on the storage and deletion of data. 

**_9\. Privacy of minors_**    
The Arredatutto website refers to a generalist audience and is not aimed at minors. We do not knowingly collect personal data from users who are considered minor under their laws.

**_10\. Owners and responsible for the protection of personal data (DPO)_**    
Any personal data provided or collected through the operations carried out on the Site will be processed by Arredatutto Srl as the independent data controller, in personal of its legal representative  _pro-tempore_  , with registered office in Milan, Via Vigevano n. 32.   
Furnishing as contracting party is the data controller and is responsible for the acquisition, use, transmission, storage and protection of personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and current legislation.   
Arredatutto has appointed a Data Protection Officer (DPO) as head of the privacy program for the data controller. For more information, write to us at info@arredatutto.com.

**_11\. How we protect your personal data_**    
We put in place all the proper means for your data to be protected. For this reason we use the technical, physical and procedural control measures that are put in place when the data are collected, processed and transferred.   
Site security is a daily work of teams dedicated to this specific task.   
In order to provide our users with the necessary security while maintaining the usual comfort of navigation, we now have several devices. We protect your personal data by adopting technical and administrative security measures to reduce the risk of loss, incorrect use, unauthorized access, disclosure and tampering of data. Among the security systems used are firewalls, data encryption, controls for the authorization of access to personal data secure protocol https.   
The connection to our site is via a secure connection using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology.

**_12\. How to exercise your rights_**    
To exercise your rights in relation to Arredatutto and / or, if necessary, obtain an oral reading of this Policy, you can decide to send your request (indicating the electronic address, name and surname, postal address and a copy of your identity document):

  * by e.mail addressing info@arredatutto.com;
  * by post sent to the following address:

Arredatutto Srl   
Via Vigevano n. 32   
20144 - Milan   
You will receive an answer within a maximum of one (1) month from the date of receipt of your request. 

In the event of your request for deletion of your data and / or exercise your right to request the deletion of your data, we may nevertheless retain it in the form of intermediate storage, for the duration necessary to meet our legal, accounting and tax and, in particular, to prevent any unlawful behavior after the cancellation of your account (re-use of your old account by a third party) and this, in accordance with applicable legislation. 

You can also at any time ask us not to send you advertising or newsletters or searches that correspond to the navigation information of your device, by contacting us directly and for free. Any advertising that you may continue to receive, unless opposed by you against us, will no longer be able to browse your device. 

You can claim a complaint at any time by contacting one of the following authorities: 

**_13\. Illicit uses_**    
However, you must protect your password and do not have to communicate it to anyone.   
We also recommend that you never disclose information that can identify you or identify a third person. If you do so, our responsibility can not in any case be brought into question in this regard. Moreover, Arredatutto asks you to contact us immediately if you notice unauthorized or suspicious use of your data in connection with Arredatutto by writing to the following e-mail address info@arredatutto.com.   
Your password and connection links to the Site sent in our electronic messages are confidential and reserved exclusively for you.   
The electronic messages received from Arredatutto, the connection links they contain and your passwords must never be transmitted to other people to avoid any risk of identity usurpation.   
Regardless of Furnishing to which you have voluntarily transmitted your Data, and taking into account the nature of the Internet network, other operators who have no connection with Arredatutto, are able to capture this information without your consent, especially when surfing the Internet. Consequently, we recommend that you install anti-virus and "anti-spyware" on your computer and update them regularly.   
In fact, despite the fact that the infrastructures of Arredatutto are protected by malicious software, the so-called "malware" (viruses, Trojans, worms, spyware ...), the responsibility for the security of your device and your network is yours. We recommend that you use an updated antivirus on your device, not to allow anyone to access your home network or your Wi-Fi and to verify that your internet communications are legitimate. You can even install a firewall on your computer.

**_14\. Usurpation / Phishing (telematic fraud aimed at acquiring personal data)_**    
Since Arredatutto does its utmost to offer you a perfectly protected navigation on the Site, your ID and password will never be requested. Arredatutto will never ask you by e-mail to communicate Personal Data or financial information. You will only disclose information about your account after connecting to the Website directly.   
If you receive an electronic message from Arredatutto that seems fraudulent, please inform us by sending it to the address: info@arredatutto.com. You must know that we work with the competent authorities to arrest and prosecute fraudsters and identity usurpers.   
If you suspect that your Arredatutto account has been usurped, immediately contact our Customer Service from Monday to Friday, from 9.30 to 17.30: telf. 02-4292871.   
In case of credit card fraud, please contact your bank.

**_15\. Security of online payments_**    
The Site is protected by one of the currently most performing protection systems. Arredatutto not only adopted the SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption method, but also reinforced all the distortion and encryption procedures to protect all the so-called "sensitive" data connected to the means of payment in the most effective way.   
When you pay on the Site, your bank details are encrypted on your device, and then transmitted in an incomprehensible way to the destination of the servers that are the only ones able to decrypt them. The authorizations and data are then verified at your bank to prevent abuse and fraud.   
This process is based on the HTTPS protocol (implementation of SSLv3 or TLSv1 over HTTP), one of the most robust of our days.   
During their transfer via the Internet, it is not possible to decrypt them: nothing transits if it is not encrypted on mobile telecommunications networks.   
At the time of payment you have the possibility to save your credit card details to facilitate your future purchases on our Website. We collect your express agreement for this purpose.   
This information is collected, recorded and protected solely by our partners in compliance with the "PCI-DSS" (Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard) security policy.   
We remind you that you must notify as soon as possible any fraudulent transaction to your bank or to the institution that issued your card.

**_16\. Social network_**    
Arredatutto is present on social networks. Whether it's fan pages or dedicated applications, our internet pages are on Facebook, Twitter, Youtube, Instagram, etc. It is recalled that access to these Social Networks requires your acceptance of their contractual conditions that imply provisions concerning the regulation governing Personal Data for the treatments carried out on them, and that independently of our pages on these Social Networks.   
For more information on the protection of your Personal Data while browsing these Social   
Moreover, the use of Social Networks may cause Cookies to be emitted from the electronic media of these Social Networks by other entities other than Arredatutto and the issue and use of Cookies by third parties and / or Partners, obey the privacy policies of these third parties and / or Partners. We inform you of the object of Cookies that we know about, issued by our Sites and the means at your disposal to make choices regarding these Cookies.

**_17\. Cookies and similar technologies_**    
When you access or interact with our sites, services, apps, tools or messaging systems, Arredatutto and our authorized service providers may use cookies and other similar technologies for advertising and marketing purposes as well as to offer you a better, faster and better experience. safer. For more information you can consult our Information on the use of cookies complete.
